<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Si Hui</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Si Hui</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing ✍︎</title>
      <link>/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/</guid>
      <description>Fermenting. ✨
Meanwhile, two newsletters: weekly meandering snippets and monthly content recommendations in collaboration with a close friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Funeral Manifesto</title>
      <link>/dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dead/</guid>
      <description>Because I am bossy, and sentimental, and simply Too Much.
The Funeral  I haven&amp;rsquo;t decided about an open/closed casket, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to be cremated in one of those eco coffins that can be written on. Write me a love note. Play all the sad soppy stuff I love best: Frank Ocean, Sufjan Stevens, Kelsey Lu, Phoebe Bridgers, Andrew Bird, Rachel Yamagata, Cigarettes After Sex, FKA twigs, Damien Rice, The Velvet Underground, slow Mandopop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/human/</guid>
      <description>Lim (family name) Si Hui (given name, yes, both words)
Writer, designer, improviser. Sitting at the intersection of experimentation, anthropology, and technology.
I&amp;rsquo;m happiest telling stories and making things work, no matter how scrappy or small. I care very much about intentionality, interiority, doing good in the world and doing it well.
In the matter of living, I am concerned with the widening of the human heart.
📮 gmail: heysihui</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meta/</guid>
      <description>v1.0 | Aug 2020 Running this site off Hugo on the Call me Sam theme and trying my darndest best to learn How To Do Front End. Have come a long way from coding blogskins in my preteen years and I am so much more easily confused by the file structures these days, despite the relative ease of Markdown and Hugo.
I&amp;rsquo;ve taken about a month of on-and-off tinkering to put this together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look At Your Fish 🐡</title>
      <link>/looking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/looking/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Attention is the beginning of devotion.&amp;rdquo; — Mary Oliver
In 2012, Robin Sloan published a tap essay-app called Fish. It extolled the value of, in the age of a fast-moving internet, returning to the things you love over and over again. Looking at your fish.
In its spirit, here are the fish in my genealogy of influence.
🌊
I saw Egon Schiele&amp;rsquo;s work in Leopold Museum one cold dark winter&amp;rsquo;s night and the world opened right up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/making/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/making/</guid>
      <description>My creative practice thrives on documentation, reflection, and lived experience. More and more, I am experimenting with the idea of reaching an understanding of the self through repetition and time-bound rituals. I make helpful things at work and thoughtful, joyful things for myself.
Designer as a Potato Snack Lil talk/exercise I ran for my team in Nov 2021. What&amp;rsquo;s your shape as a designer?
A Funeral Manifesto Post-demise planning; always iterating as I learn from being alive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>